

Dmitry KomissarovProduct designer

Portfolio

behance.net/MN_Des

Here is my works avaiible for public.

"Naked" works t.me/nacked_works

"Naked" means works haven't been edited for portfolio.

About me

I worked as a print designer at freelance platforms, but after all I found myself as an UI/UX designer.

Out of office I work as freelancer. I have customers from USA, Dubai, Poland, Russia, Ukraine. Most of them work with me for more than 7 years.

Phone

+380958395025

Mail

mn.design.04@gmail.com

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/mn-design

Telegram

t.me/MN_Design



SKILLS

Strong

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Lightroom, FontLab Studio, Corel Draw X, Adobe XD, Adobe Indesign

Familiar

Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects, 3Ds Max

Languages

Native in Russian & Ukrainian and conversational in English

EXPERIENCE

Feb 2004 — Present • 16 years

Freelance

Product Designer, UI/UX Designer, Print Designer

May 2017 — Oct 2019 • 2 years

SKIF

UI/UX Designer, Print Designer

- Android app for training soldiers of Ukraine Army (Ministry of Defence);
- Exhibition areas & print materials in USA, Germany, Ukraine.

Sep 2016 — Sep 2019 · 3 years

Lasertag.net / Space Arena / Airbunker Graphic Designer, Print Designer

- Phone&TV Android apps;
- Brand identity, logo and all print materials;
- Brand Airbunker was a sponsor of World Paintball Championship, this logo printed almost every big paintball field in the world;
- Exhibition areas & print materials in Ukraine, Russia, USA, Germany, Spain, Italy, England, etc.

Oct 2015 — Sep 2016 • 11 months

Magpress

Print Designer

- Print materials fo government and private hospitals;
- Work with plotter cutter and non-paper materials (plastic, acrylic and other).

Apr 2015 — Oct 2015 • 6 months

Sparrow Hills

Graphic Designer

- Posters for subway;
- Posters of the size of 24-floor buildings;
- Posters for billboards.

Mar 2015 - May 2015 • 3 months

Promodo

Graphic Designer

- Web-posters of social media marketing (Rozetka, EVA, AnyWayAnyDay, DEKO, Metro).

Jun 2014 — Sep 2014 • 3 months

Mobilluck

Graphic Designer

- Web-posters of social media marketing;
- Print materials, brand identity, logos, icons.

EDUCATION

2010 — 2014 • 4 years

Kharkiv Petro Vasylenko National Technical University of Agriculture

Computer Programming

2005 — 2010 · 4 years

Kharkiv Mashynobudivnyy College Industry engineering

1997 - 2005 • 8 years

Specialized School of I-III levels Nº 119

Phone

+380958395025

Mail

mn.design.04@gmail.com

Linkedin

Linkedin.com/in/mn-design

Telegram

t.me/MN_Design

